

CONTACT

Address
Sahlian Maldialan Tehsil &
District Bagh (AJK)

Phone
0347-8092378
0311-5253693

EDUCATION

2010 **MATRICULATION**

FG Public High School Bagh (AJK)

2012 ICS

National Science College Bagh (AJK)

2016
BS (CS)
University of AJK Muzaffarabad

SKILLS

Git & Azure DevOps for version control

Proficient in JavaScript & TypeScript

Strong Angular 14 skills

ASP.NET & ASP.NET Core Web API development

Jira for project management & agile methodologies

Microsoft SQL server 2014 +

Knowledge of algorithms and data structures $% \left(x\right) =\left(x\right) +\left(x\right)$

Problem-solving and analytical skills

IRFAN FAZAL

FULL STACK DEVELOPER
Angular 14 & ASP.NET/.NET Core

PROFILE

Agile Scrum software engineer with 2 years of experience in developing billing software modules, adding reports, and implementing new features using .NET and Angular technologies. Skilled in version control, Git, and Azure, with a strong problem-solving ability and passion for staying up-to-date with emerging technologies.

EXPERIENCE

2018-Present
MTBC CARECLOUD

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- Have to follow the entire software development cycle and provide comprehensive support.
- Develop SQL scripts that extract, load, and transform data based on business needs while maintaining data integrity.
- Develops software solutions by studying information needs; conferring with users; studying systems flow.
- Data usage, and work processes; investigating problem areas; following the software development lifecycle.
- Review existing software code and optimization it.
- Responsible for analysis of current programs including performance, diagnosis and troubleshooting of problem programs, and designing solutions to problematic programming.
- Participated in sprint planning and reviews, contributing ideas for future development and identifying areas for improvement.
- Enhanced existing modules by updating functionality, fixing bugs, and improving performance to better meet user needs.
- Worked as part of an Agile Scrum team responsible for developing billing software modules, adding reports, and implementing new features based on business requirements.

July 2018 - Dec 2018

ERPIN Technologies Private Limited Check Shahzad (Rawalpindi)

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- Testing and debugging
- Documenting code
- Writing code
- Contributing to the team's process improvement
- Learning new technologies
- Meeting deadlines and milestones

July 2017-July 2018

Solume Science Technologies (Rawalpindi)

IT INTERN

- Learning new technologies.
- Assisting with IT support.
- Participating in projects
- Conducting research
- Shadowing senior staffCollaborating with team members
- Maintaining documentation
- · Attending meetings